{
    "id": "fc491b05d1334516a00978635f97c17a",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The thief jumped ........................ the wall.",
            "description": "Over is used to say on or to the other side of something high.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked ............................ the fields.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "in",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat .............................. her son and daughter.",
            "description": "Use between to talk about two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "amongst"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We drove ............................. the tunnel.",
            "description": "Use through for movement within spaces where there are things all around.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "in",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you staring ............................. me?",
            "description": "Use at with look, stare etc.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They took over a week to cross the Atlantic ............................... a ship.",
            "description": "We use on with bus, train, plane and ship.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They live ......................................... the third floor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that pretty girl .............................. the second row?",
            "description": "We use in a row.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "London is ........................... river Thames.",
            "description": "Use on to show position on a line.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You should never run ............................... the road.",
            "description": "Across shows movement from one side to the other side.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "along",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I first met him .............................. a department store.",
            "description": "In shows position inside. Use at with proper nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been ages ............................... I heard anything from her.",
            "description": "Use since with the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}